<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New Maps Plus templates</title>
    <link>https://newmapsplus.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on New Maps Plus templates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 08:24:48 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://newmapsplus.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Map673</title>
      <link>https://newmapsplus.github.io/courses/map673/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 08:24:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newmapsplus.github.io/courses/map673/</guid>
      <description>MAP 673-201: Programming for Web Mapping Course description MAP673 integrates the principles of geographic representation and web programming in order for students to develop high-quality interactive web maps. Students will design interactive web map projects that appropriately represent spatial data in order to serve end-user goals of map engagement and visual communication. The course will train students to compose interactive maps within the context of a coherent web page layout, including the development of supplementary content (such as text and metadata) to aid in visual storytelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Map672</title>
      <link>https://newmapsplus.github.io/courses/map672/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 08:24:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newmapsplus.github.io/courses/map672/</guid>
      <description>MAP 672: Programming for Web Mapping Course Description This course introduces students to the fundamental concepts and techniques of web development and computer programming through web mapping. Students will become familiar with current web standards and proficient in manipulating the structural, stylistic and behavioral elements of web maps through programming. Students will translate these practices to achieve objectives in web cartography such as the display of a basemap, the thematic representation of data, and the employment of interaction to enhance visual communication and the presentation of information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Column</title>
      <link>https://newmapsplus.github.io/examples/two-column/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 12:38:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newmapsplus.github.io/examples/two-column/</guid>
      <description>Content Coffee so sugar, saucer irish seasonal acerbic arabica bar mazagran body blue mountain. Robust seasonal filter iced blue mountain cup irish. Saucer cinnamon plunger pot pumpkin spice, robusta cultivar, to go, decaffeinated grinder shop crema cortado. Coffee so sugar, saucer irish seasonal acerbic arabica bar mazagran body blue mountain. Robust seasonal filter iced blue mountain cup irish. Saucer cinnamon plunger pot pumpkin spice, robusta cultivar, to go, decaffeinated grinder shop crema cortado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scroll</title>
      <link>https://newmapsplus.github.io/examples/scroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 07:54:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newmapsplus.github.io/examples/scroll/</guid>
      <description>Item 1 Item 2 Item 3 Item 4   Welcome to an adventure in maps Coffee so sugar, saucer irish seasonal acerbic arabica bar mazagran body blue mountain. Robust seasonal filter iced blue mountain cup irish. Saucer cinnamon plunger pot pumpkin spice, robusta cultivar, to go, decaffeinated grinder shop crema cortado. Fair trade, a café au lait, sit plunger pot macchiato medium organic chicory macchiato caramelization. White, et, est single origin, java aged turkish trifecta rich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fullscreen Offcanvas</title>
      <link>https://newmapsplus.github.io/examples/fullscreen-offcanvas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 15:58:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newmapsplus.github.io/examples/fullscreen-offcanvas/</guid>
      <description> blah blah -- Map Information     Offcanvas right   ...   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hearts</title>
      <link>https://newmapsplus.github.io/courses/hearts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:47:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newmapsplus.github.io/courses/hearts/</guid>
      <description>😂😂😂😂😂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Map671</title>
      <link>https://newmapsplus.github.io/courses/map671/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 12:00:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newmapsplus.github.io/courses/map671/</guid>
      <description>MAP 671: Introduction to New Mapping NewMapsPlus.github.io
Course Description This course introduces students to both the social and technical aspects of digital mapping in the 21st century. Students will learn fundamental concepts and techniques in cartography and GIS, including file types, spatial databases, data manipulation, projections and coordinate reference systems, and analytical and spatial analysis techniques in a range of desktop, server, and web-based mapping platforms. In addition to providing the fundamental technical competencies necessary to create maps, students will develop the critical awareness required to effectively communicate complex social processes through maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fullscreen</title>
      <link>https://newmapsplus.github.io/examples/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 11:37:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newmapsplus.github.io/examples/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description>  blah blah -- Map Information     Modal title   Modal body text goes here.
 Close      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Map</title>
      <link>https://newmapsplus.github.io/map/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 13:55:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newmapsplus.github.io/map/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A</title>
      <link>https://newmapsplus.github.io/a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 13:51:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newmapsplus.github.io/a/</guid>
      <description>Hello World Alligators aer everywhere
yes, it&amp;rsquo;s true </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
